Contact

istiak.ahmed227@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/istiak227 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

User Interface Design IT Business Analysis Entrepreneurship

Certifications

Machine Learning Using SAS

Istiak Ahmed

Web Developer | Aspiring UI/UX Designer Dhaka

Summary

Experienced web application developer with a demonstrated history of working in the publishing industry. Skilled in IT Business Analysis, UI/UX designing, Python (Programming Language), JS, and Back-End Web Development. Strong engineering professional with a Bachelor of Information Technology focused in IT technology from HELP University.

Experience

Traideas Technology
Web Designer
January 2021 - Present (1 month)
Bangladesh

FoodCompass
Managing Director
April 2020 - Present (10 months)

Narayanganj District, Dhaka, Bangladesh

FoodCompass is a start-up food guide and delivery application for bringing the user an authentic taste of the city.

Self-employed Web Application Developer February 2020 - December 2020 (11 months) Narayanganj District, Dhaka, Bangladesh

I develop front-end web applications.

Star Media Group Berhad Intern June 2019 - August 2019 (3 months) Damansara, Selangor, Malaysia

Education

HELP University

Bachelor of information technology, It technology · (2015 - 2020)

Zero To Mastery Academy